var questions = [{
	question: "What show involved a yellow dish washing tool that lived at the bottom of the sea?",
	option1: "The Wild Thornberrys",
	option2: "All That!",
	option3: "Spongebob Squarepants",
	option4: "Clarissa Explains It All",
	answer: "Spongebob Squarepants",
	}, 
	{
	question: "In the show titled Rugrats, what were the names of the two twins?",
	option1: "Huey and Duey",
	option2: "Philip and Lilian",
	option3: "Dillan and Jilian",
	option4: "Sarah and Steven",
	answer: "Philip and Lilian",
	},
	{
	question: "What was the name of Rocko's best friend in Rocko's Modern Life?",
	option1: "Heffer",
	option2: "Ren",
	option3: "Barry",
	option4: "Terry",
	answer: "Heffer",
	},
	{
	question: "What is the name of the character that Doug had a crush on?",
	option1: "Tippi Dink",
	option2: "Beebee Bluff",
	option3: "Connie Benge",
	option4: "Patti Mayonnaise",
	answer: "Patti Mayonnaise",
	},
	{
	question: "In the show, Good Burger, what was the name of the restaurant that threatened Good Burger's existence?",
	option1: "Super Burger",
	option2: "Ultra Burger",
	option3: "Mega Burger",
	option4: "Mondo Burger",
	answer: "Mondo Burger",
	},
	{
	question: "What was Helga Pataki's favorite nickname for Arnold?",
	option1: "Airhead",
	option2: "Football Head",
	option3: "Pip Squeak",
	option4: "Geek Face",
	answer: "Football Head",
	},
	{
	question: "What is the name of the mountain that contestants had to climb in the show, Global Guts?",
	option1: "Crazy Cliff",
	option2: "Danger Doom",
	option3: "Aggro Crag",
	option4: "Globo Mountain",
	answer: "Aggro Crag",
	},
	{
	question: "What Nickelodeon show involved contestants competing in video game trivia and playing against the Video Game Wizard?",
	option1: "Nick Arcade",
	option2: "Game to Fame",
	option3: "Nick Game Channel",
	option4: "Virtual Challenger",
	answer: "Nick Arcade",
	},
	{
	question: "What is the name of the show where a girl gains powers due to being drenched by a chemical spill?",
	option1: "The Amanda Show",
	option2: "Zoey 101",
	option3: "The Adventures of Pete and Pete",
	option4: "The Secret World of Alex Mack",
	answer: "The Secret World of Alex Mac",
	},
	{
	question: "What is the name of the character that kept a Slam Book about all of her friends?",
	option1: "Harriet",
	option2: "Hannah",
	option3: "Heather",
	option4: "Haley",
	answer: "Harriet",
	}];